

www.trangerthings.com www.behance.net/trangtt42714e5 trangtt427@gmail.com (925) 352-3373



PROFILE

A creative thinker with 7+ years of combined UX design, visual design and print experience. I like to approach design issues with the capacity of a user, thinking about the best ways to communicate a business goal in the simplest form.



EXPERIENCE

Controlco - UX Designer/Front End Developer

September 2016 - October 2017

- Collaborated with a building automations team to create IoT applications, both mobile and desktop, for clients to control facility operational settings.
- Designed and developed dashboards, alarm consoles, and other entities to track building innerworkings using HTML/CSS, some javascript, Niagara 4 and DGLux5.
- Designed interfaces that allowed clients to interact with cloud data from installed equipment.
- Provided wireframes, user storyboards, mock-ups, and prototypes using tools like Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, and Illustrator.

Freelance - Graphic Designer

August 2008 - Current

- Design both digital and print collateral using Illustrator, Photoshop, and InDesign.
- Ideate and provide artistic critique of client ideas.
- Create digital paintings and scalable graphics.

Mt. Diablo High School - Digital Arts Tutor

August 2008 - December 2010

- Taught sophomores how to use Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop), Flash, and Final Cut.
- Challenged students to come up with ideas and solutions to proposed issues in design.
- Mentored students and provided artistic critiqe in coursework.
- Managed classroom digital equipment.



EDUCATION

University of California, Santa Barbara 2012 - 2014

B.S. Biology, emphasis in psychobiology

Diablo Valley College 2008 - 2012

A.A. Biology Other focuses: graphic design, painting with watercolors, 2D animation, architecture, psychology



AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Skills

Gathering data

Lo-fi & hi-fi mock-ups

Wireframing & storyboarding

HTML/CSS

Graphic design

Color theory

Typography

Iconography

Prototyping

Petting cats

Software

Sketch

InVision

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

AutoCAD

Final Cut